<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Waldmann Enterprises</title>
    <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Waldmann Enterprises</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waldmannenterprises.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Process</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/the-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/the-process/</guid>
      <description>If it can be cut, we can cut it!
However, some materials are better suited for certain cutting processes - if you are unsure of the best way, just ask us! Some materials, such as Polycarbonate, cannot be lasered due to harmful fumes released when burned.
What is required? To receive a quote you must submit a drawing (.pdf), 3D model (.stp, .igs, .xt, etc.), or vector file (.svg, .dxf, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Design</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/product-design/</guid>
      <description>We design! from your idea, napkin sketch, broken parts, legacy blueprints or CAD files. 3D Scanning soon to come.
We can modify your designs to lower manufacturing costs.
Have an idea? Give us a call! We can provide the detailed drawings manufacturers require to make parts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Machining</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-machining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-machining/</guid>
      <description>We offer customer-oriented precision, fast!
About Machining
What can we cut? The material and size determines what machine will be required to cut your part. We can machine parts ranging from millimeter-sized to 4x8feet:
 Non-ferrous Soft Metals (Aluminum, Brass, Copper) Hard metals (Carbon &amp;amp; stainless steels, titanium, etc) Plastics (Acrylic, Polycarbonate, ABS, Nylon, Delrin, HDPE, PVC, Foams, etc.) Wood (Softwoods, Hardwoods, MDF, Bamboo, Laminates, etc.) Composites (Fiberglass, Carbon fiber, CFRPs, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Laser</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-laser/</guid>
      <description>We can laser cut your design, artwork or product!
What can we cut? The material determines what laser will be required to cut your part. We have both fiber &amp;amp; CO2 lasers to cut nearly all materials - if it can be cut, we can cut it!
 Plastics (Acrylic, Polycarbonate, ABS, Delrin, HDPE, PVC, Starboard, Foams, etc.) Wood (Softwoods, Hardwoods, MDF, Bamboo, Laminates, etc.) Soft Metals (Aluminum, Brass, Copper) Composites (Fiberglass, Carbonfiber, CFRPs, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sneeze Guards</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</guid>
      <description>Is your medical office or reception area looking to protect their employees and comply with suggested CDC guidelines during the COVID-19 pandemic? Do you want a simple, aesthetically pleasing, crystal clear barrier with a clean look that matches your professional office?
We can come to you to assess the area, measure, and discuss options. We develop a 3D rendering for your review and approval. Then we manufacture, deliver and install, with face masks and white gloves on for cleanliness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>For a quote, inquiry, or to schedule an on-site consult for custom sneeze guard installations CONTACT US TODAY!
Like and follow us on Social media @Dora_Designs_and_Signs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Waldmann Enterprises is located in beautiful Mount Dora, just outside of Orlando, FL.
We service all of Central Florida, including: Sanford, Lake Mary, Apopka, Oviedo, Winter Park, Maitland, Altamonte, Ocoee, Winter Garden, Clermont, Minneola, Leesburg, Tavares, and The Villages.
Capabilities/equipment Our current equipment includes:
 4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo; 3-axis CNC router dual spindle with 8 tool ATC 24&amp;quot;x20&amp;quot;x20&amp;quot; CNC Mill 22&amp;quot;x16&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot; CNC Mill w/ 4th axis 5&amp;rsquo;x10&amp;rsquo; FIBER CNC Laser 4&amp;rsquo;x3&amp;rsquo; CO2 CNC Laser Miller 325 engine-driven welder for mobile fabrication, repairs &amp;amp; backup power generation multiple 3D Printers for rapid prototyping, molds and samples supporting manual cutting/drilling/pressing/sanding and QC inspection equipment  About the Owner Owner/operator Jon Waldmann started Waldmann Enterprises in May 2020 in pursuit of a fullfilling, hands-on career merging his technical talents and creative desires.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
