<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Waldmann Enterprises</title>
    <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Waldmann Enterprises</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://waldmannenterprises.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Carved Signs</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/outdoor-carved-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/outdoor-carved-signs/</guid>
      <description>An extremely durable, UV &amp;amp; Weatherproof, HDPE solution for the outdoors and Florida sun. Guaranteed not to rust, delaminate or rot. Available in a variety colors.
Can be used as: Home address, street or parking signs, monograms and names, entrance gates, mail box numbers, path and park signs, marine and recreational applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Development &amp; Improvement / CNC Training</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/the-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/the-process/</guid>
      <description>Great things happen when you work SMARTER and HARDER. We help our clients run faster, more parts per cycle, and with less scrap, OR get setup from the ground up.
Whether you struggle with tooling selection, programming challenging features, long cycle times, inconsistent workholding, or designing for manufacturability - we can help you!
Take full advantage of your existing equipment by using the advanced features you may not know exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Design &amp; CAD/CAM</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/product-design/</guid>
      <description>We design and program! from your idea, napkin sketch, broken parts, legacy blueprints or CAD files. We can also provide remote or on-site CAM programming solutions.
Already have a design? We can improve designs to lower manufacturing costs.
Unlike many design houses, we have much more than just CAD software. We can print, machine, or laser cut 1000&amp;rsquo;s of parts for your company or project.
Have an idea? Give us a call!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Machining</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-machining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-machining/</guid>
      <description>We offer customer-oriented, precision parts, fast!
We can cut metal, plastic and composites to your specification. Milling is our specialty; 1 part or 1000&amp;rsquo;s, prototypes or blanket PO production.
Don&amp;rsquo;t have models or drawings? We can assist in development. Contact us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Cutting / Engraving</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-laser/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-laser/</guid>
      <description>We can laser cut your design, artwork or product!
What can we cut? The material type determines what laser will be required to cut your part. We have both fiber &amp;amp; CO2 lasers to cut nearly all materials - if it can be cut, we can cut it!
Plastics (Acrylic, Polycarbonate, ABS, Delrin, HDPE, PVC, Starboard, Foams, etc.) Wood (Softwoods, Hardwoods, MDF, Bamboo, Laminates, etc.) Soft Metals (Aluminum, Brass, Copper) Composites (Fiberglass, Carbonfiber, CFRPs, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing &amp; Rapid Prototyping</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/3d-printing-rapid-prototyping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/3d-printing-rapid-prototyping/</guid>
      <description>We can have parts in your hands FAST!
Revisions of your product can be iterated quickly, with low cost filaments until a final design is achieved.
Then, depending on the application, prototypes can be printed in one several material types such as ABS, Nylon or Carbon Fiber reinforced filaments; OR we can machine the parts from metal if required.
Unlike many design houses, we have much more than just 3D-printers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Routing</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-routing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/cnc-routing/</guid>
      <description>Similiar to machining, our advanced CNC router can handle complex geometries, but on a much larger scale or give the ability to nest many shapes in one setup to reduce overall costs. This process can handle dusty composites, fiberglass, plastics, or woods that one not suited for machining centers.
Don&amp;rsquo;t have models, drawings or dxfs? We can help you develop those. Email us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sheet and Panel Cutting</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/sheet-and-panel-cutting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/services/sheet-and-panel-cutting/</guid>
      <description>We can turn a pallet of sheet material into shapes or kitted bundles and deliver it to your door. Wood, Plastics, Composites, Metal. Simple shapes or complex geometries.
Don&amp;rsquo;t have models, drawings or dxfs? We can help you develop those. Email us today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switch Panels / Instrument Clusters / Enclosures</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/switch-panels-and-instrument-clusters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/switch-panels-and-instrument-clusters/</guid>
      <description>Simple to complex switch plates, gauge clusters, instrumentation panels, enclosures. For marine, automotive, recreational, consumer electronics, communications and laboratory applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display Cases / Fume Hoods</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/display-cases-and-fume-hoods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/display-cases-and-fume-hoods/</guid>
      <description>Clear or colored fume and dust hoods for Laboratory or testing environments. Bases or feet can be added for your application. Display stands and cases for valuables, artwork, POS, Collectibles, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Engraving Blanks</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/laser-engraving-blanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/laser-engraving-blanks/</guid>
      <description>
Tired of the same cheap imported blanks for your laser engraving business? Need a custom shape, size, thickness, or material?
We can provide quick turnaround on 1 to 1000&amp;rsquo;s of coins, nameplates, plaques, EDC tools, etc&amp;hellip;
Made in the USA using CNC laser cutting, milling, turning or stamping
Have an idea? Give us a call! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HD Labels and Tags</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/hd-labels-and-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/hd-labels-and-tags/</guid>
      <description>Heavy gage labels &amp;amp; tags with easy to read, permanent marking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sneeze Guards / Partitions</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/custom-sneeze-guards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/products/custom-sneeze-guards/</guid>
      <description>Simple, aesthetically pleasing, crystal clear partitions / barriers with a clean look that matches your professional office.
We can come to you to assess the area, measure, and discuss options. We develop a 3D rendering for your review and approval. Then we manufacture, deliver and install, with a white glove treatment for cleanliness.
We make all of our parts in-house so we can add features such as temperature scanning windows or add extra pass thru windows to meet your process requirements at your medical office or reception area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>For a quote, inquiry, or to schedule a video or on-site consultation - CONTACT US TODAY! What is required for a quote? In order to quote on a per part basis, a drawing (.pdf), 3D model (.sldprt, .stp, .igs, .xt, etc.), or vector file (.svg, .dxf, .ai, etc.) We also need the material type and specific tolerances or fitments; please provide a drawing so we can ensure a perfect part every time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Waldmann Enterprises is located in beautiful Mount Dora, Florida, in the greater Orlando area. About the Owner Owner/operator Jon Waldmann started Waldmann Enterprises in 2020 in pursuit of a fullfilling, hands-on, career merging his technical talents and creative desires. Jon graduated from UCF with a BS in Mechanical Engineering and spent 7 years in medical product design and CNC manufacturing. As a gear-head with a black belt and a passion for the outdoors, he is not afraid of challenges that may require developing unconventional methods to achieve desired output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://waldmannenterprises.com/capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://waldmannenterprises.com/capabilities/</guid>
      <description>Waldmann Enterprises is equipped with many advanced CNC controlled cutting machines to handle most any material or need; along with the workholding, tools, inspection equipment, software, and experience to utilize the machines to their full extent.
Core Competencies Engineering Services Product Design - Develop your ideas or sketches into working prototypes CAD/CAM - 3D modeling and toolpath generation with advanced softwares Reverse Engineering - Creation of CAD data from a physical component you supply Process Improvement - Run more efficiently, consistently and quickly while reducing errors and non-conformances CNC training - Increase productivity by increasing your knowledge of controls, softwares, G-code and machining techniques Design for Manufacturing (DFM) consulting - Improvement of your designs to reduce cost or cycle times Tool and die design - Custom cutting or forming tools for your machines or operations Manfacturing Services Rapid Prototyping (3d printing, low volume machining or laser) Production CNC Machining, Routing, Laser cutting Production 3D printing Product Marking / Engraving - Laser or Milled White labeling, Blanket PO &amp;amp; Just-In-Time Agreements Or we can come to you - Setup, programming and optimization of client&amp;rsquo;s machines, processes &amp;amp; operations Equipment YCM NXV-560A - 22&amp;quot;x16&amp;quot;x18&amp;quot; Vertical Mill w/ 4th axis SHARP SV-2420 - 24&amp;quot;x20&amp;quot;x20&amp;quot; Vertical Mill 4&amp;rsquo;x8&amp;rsquo; CNC router, dual spindle, ATC, Vacuum table, 8ft rotary axis 4&amp;rsquo;x3&amp;rsquo; 150W CO2 CNC Laser Galvo Fiber Marking laser Variety of 3D printers for rapid prototyping supporting manual cutting/drilling/pressing/deburring and QC equipment SolidWorks, Fusion 360, Lightburn, V-carve What can we cut?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
