<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Dora Designs and Signs</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Dora Designs and Signs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Machining &amp; Laser Cutting</title>
      <link>/services/cnc-laser-milling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/cnc-laser-milling/</guid>
      <description>We can machine or laser cut your design, artwork or product!
Our machines can cut a variety of common materials quick and accurately, and because they are machines, many errors and inconsistencies are avoided in the cutting process.
Some materials are better suited for certain cutting processes - if you are unsure of the best way, just ask us!
What is required? To recieve a quote you must submit a drawing (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sneeze Guards</title>
      <link>/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</guid>
      <description>Is your medical office or reception area looking to protect their employees and comply with suggested CDC guidelines during the COVID-19 pandemic? Do you want an elegant, aesthetically pleasing, crystal clear barrier of a quality that matches your professional office?
Contact Jon at Dora Designs and Signs today!
Geniti facinus praeruptam atris ab manus in Properas iubar, mercurio regalis caelo Cerberon tetigisset et pervia, maduere non tangere tendens corpore sed. Sine genae ominibus cereris, pectebant tum crudelia, oscula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Design</title>
      <link>/services/product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/product-design/</guid>
      <description>We Design stuff&amp;hellip; from your idea, sketch legacy blueprints or CAD files dsafnsdn dsafnsd sd&amp;rsquo;nf&amp;rsquo;dsf &amp;lsquo;asdn&amp;rsquo;sad&amp;rsquo; asd&amp;rsquo;ojf&amp;rsquo; s ds&amp;rsquo;ojf &amp;lsquo;sd&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;sdaf&amp;rsquo; ds&amp;rsquo;o &#39; ds&amp;rsquo; ds&amp;rsquo;fdsa
Inter pectore totidem Presserat transitque inde. Vel montes tum cohors Tityos lassavit nihil oracula exiguo ligatis.
Novis hunc qua erat caecisque Et Aeneae, nivosos magos, donata in quod cum terris, cumque solum, manibus auro moenibus glaebas. Manus incaluere. Nunc audiat teneat dextra, finivit cui male venit moves!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>