<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Dora Designs and Signs</title>
    <link>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Dora Designs and Signs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNC Machining &amp; Laser Cutting</title>
      <link>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/cnc-laser-milling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/cnc-laser-milling/</guid>
      <description>We can machine or laser cut your design, artwork or product!
We can also add engravings, markings or burning to an existing product. Add a permanent logo, artwork, lasered image, or special message for a life event. Phone cases, knives, Ipads, cutting boards, glasses, just to name a few.
Some materials are better suited for certain cutting processes - if you are unsure of the best way, just ask us! Some materials, such as Vinyl, cannot be lasered due to harmful fumes released when burned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sneeze Guards</title>
      <link>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/custom-sneeze-guards/</guid>
      <description>Is your medical office or reception area looking to protect their employees and comply with suggested CDC guidelines during the COVID-19 pandemic? Do you want a simple, aesthetically pleasing, crystal clear barrier with a clean look that matches your professional office?
We can come to you to assess the area, measure, and discuss options. We develop a 3D rendering for your review and approval. Then we manufacture, deliver and install, with face masks and white gloves on for cleanliness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Design</title>
      <link>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doradesignsandsigns.com/services/product-design/</guid>
      <description>We design! from your idea, napkin sketch, broken parts, legacy blueprints or CAD files.
We can modify your designs to lower manufacturing costs.
Have an idea? Give us a call! We can provide the detailed drawings manufacturers require to make parts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
